http://buygolfshirts.com/terms_privacy.asp

Go!
Privacy Policy
BuyGolfShirts.com is very sensitive to the privacy concerns of the visitors to its site on the Internet. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from visitors to the site. However, certain non-personal information of visitors is recorded by the standard operation of buygolfshirts.com Internet servers. This information is primarily used to provide an enhanced online experience for the visitor. Information tracked includes the type of operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) and the type of browser being used by the visitor (e.g., FireFox, Chrome, etc.).
Other uses of this information include internal review of the number of visitors to the site but only in an aggregate and non-personally identifiable form. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information such as a first and last name, home or other physical address, telephone number, about visitors to this site are known only when voluntarily submitted for example via registration for purchasing privileges, content submissions, suggestions or participation of visitors in any available online interactive activities.
Unless otherwise disclosed during the collection, personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors to this site is retained by buygolfshirts.com and is not sold, transferred or otherwise disclosed outside the company, except where disclosure is required by law. This information may be used for any of the following purposes: (1) to help buygolfshirts.com better understand visitors' use of our site; (2) to fulfill orders; (3) to respond to specific requests from our visitors;(4) to provide any necessary notices to our visitors or their parent or guardians, where necessary; (5) to protect the security or integrity of our site when necessary.
To the extent that any of the sites accessible through buygolfshirts.com web site have different practices, those different practices will be applicable at those sites.
Use of Cookies
When you view our web site, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor the site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Acceptance of Privacy Terms and Conditions
Your access to and use of this site is subject to the above privacy terms and conditions and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, these terms and conditions. buygolfshirts.com may at any time revise these privacy terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then current privacy terms and conditions to which you are bound.
If you have questions regarding the BuyGolfShirts.com Privacy Statement, please
contact us.
